

AURORA GEORGES

aurorageorges@hotmail.com | +47 412 89 467 | 550000 Da Nang My An 5, Vietnam | www.aurorageorges.com

PROFILE

Bachelor degree in Digital Art Design at Hedmark University of Applied Sciences, with 1 year experience as Junior 2D concept artist at Gameloft in Vietnam. Specialized character design, concept art and illustration, with basic understanding of 3D-sculpting and 2D-animation. Fast learner, motivated and passionate artist with a strong desire to create artwork for games.

LANGUAGES

Norwegian • Native English • Fluent French • Bilingual

EXPERIENCE

JAN 2018 - CURRENT

JUNIOR 2D CONCEPT ARTIST, GAMELOFT

 Description and and an explanation are

Drawing concept art and marketing illustrations for games

JUNE 2017 - DEC 2017

• FREELANCER, PROUDER AS

Drawing logos for high school-graduates

JULY 2016 - MARCH 2017 • INTERNSHIP, RETROGENE AS

Drawing character designs, making storyboards, create in-game layouts

EDUCATION

AUG 2013 – JUNE 2016 • HEDMARK UNIVERSITY OF APPLIED SCIENCES,

DEPT. HAMAR

Bachelor in Digital Art and Design

AUG 2010 - JUNE 2013 • PORSGRUNN HIGH SCHOOL

General studies with specialization in art

REFERENCES

Hugo Maximiliano Cadiz

• Studio Lead Artist at Gameloft

E-mail:

teseo_arcadio@hotmail.com

Phone • +84 96 390 17 57

KEY SKILLS • **SOFTWARE PROFICIENCY**

Character design
Illustration
Concept art
Animal & creature design
UI elements

Adobe Photoshop CC Adobe After Effects Basic Autodesk Maya Basic Adobe Flash